<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>kursy - Category - notes in hugo</title>
        <link>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/categories/kursy/</link>
        <description>kursy - Category - notes in hugo</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/categories/kursy/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Mindshift, a course on learning - week 2</title>
    <link>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/posts/mindshift-learning-2/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/posts/mindshift-learning-2/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Mindshift: Break Through Obstacles to Learning and Discover Your Hidden Potential by McMaster University on Coursera
Week 1
Week 2 Advantage of poor memory Because there are roughly 4 working memory slots in the brain and 4 memory/thought neural chunks can be held there at any given moment, pulling in or losing active chunks from working memory activates diffuse mode and results in more creative solutions to problems.
Meditation types and brain moded focus meditation (sound, mantra, chakra)]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Mindshift, a course on learning - week 3</title>
    <link>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/posts/mindshift-learning-3/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/posts/mindshift-learning-3/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Mindshift: Break Through Obstacles to Learning and Discover Your Hidden Potential by McMaster University on Coursera
Week 1 Week 2
Week 3 noradrenaline interconnected with serotonin: mental and physical activity, sustained motivation and drive
dopamine high levels good mood, energized, extroverted increased weight of reward (thus key in positive reinforcement training) goes up with unexpected reward appearance goes down with non-appearance of an expected reward
Pushback dabble learn gradually and slowly, and grow with the change, letting others adapt]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Tarot z Codecademy</title>
    <link>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/posts/codecademy-tarot/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/posts/codecademy-tarot/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Codecademy przy wszystkich swoich zaletach ma czasem ćwiczenia, któe są nudne i strasznie powtarzalne, ale ma też takie, które inspirują żeby zostać z nimi chwilę dłużej i trochę rozbudować. W tym przypadku chodziło o wyciągnięcie ze słownika sztywno przypisanych kluczy razem z wartościami i pokazanie ich w trzech linijkach tekście.
Zwykłe ćwicznie niby nic, ale fakt że wartościami są karty tarota a teksty układają się w prostą &ldquo;wróżbę&rdquo;, daje potencjał. Wystarczyło dodać losowanie kart w funkcji (oryginalnie to była lista wybranych wartości) i można się przez chwilę pobawić.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Mindshift, a course on learning</title>
    <link>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/posts/mindshift-learning/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/posts/mindshift-learning/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Mindshift: Break Through Obstacles to Learning and Discover Your Hidden Potential by McMaster University on Coursera
Week 1 The unexpected assets from your past&ndash;and breaking through initial feelings of incompetence This is not entirely unexpected: I&rsquo;ve been a hobbyist programmer for around 30 years now, started as a kid, then on and off used simple scripts for work and bits and pieces of web design for personal projects. At work I&rsquo;ve been meeting IT managers and experienced developers and felt a great gap between their expertise and my limited understanding of programming.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Matlab - IDE vs notepad</title>
    <link>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/posts/matlab-first-function/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/posts/matlab-first-function/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Matlab na forum Coursery w kursie mnóstwo ludzi ma problem z napisaniem pierwszej funkcji w testach - nie otwierają się w edytorze na https://matlab.mathworks.com/ tylko w zwykłym textboksie. Tymczasem&hellip;
edytor funkcji otwiera się z gotowym szablonem
1 2 3 4 5 6  function[outputArg1,outputArg2] =untitled2(inputArg1,inputArg2)%UNTITLED2 Summary of this function goes here % Detailed explanation goes here outputArg1 = inputArg1; outputArg2 = inputArg2; end   min i max w ćwiczeniu w środku tygodnia główny cel to chyba zmuszenie ludzi do zajrzenia do dokumentacji, bo ma bardzo niewiele wspólnego z filmami z tego tygodnia]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Python: list comprehension</title>
    <link>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/posts/python-list-compregension/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/posts/python-list-compregension/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[cała lista new_list = [element.method() for element in old_list]
wrunkowo z if new_list = [element.method() for element in old_list if element = &ldquo;chosen&rdquo;]
warunkowo z if/else new_list = [element.method() if element != &ldquo;exception&rdquo; else element.exception_method() for element in old_list]]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>notatki z git</title>
    <link>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/posts/notes-on-git/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://krzysiekwie.github.io/hugowie/posts/notes-on-git/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[notatki z kursu o git na Courserze Większość materiałów pochodzi z Coursery
on setting new email and privacy
git init git clone URL
git init creates .git/ (git directory) in the current directory, the &ldquo;working tree&rdquo; is the current/parent directory that contains .git/
The git directory contains all the changes and their history and the working tree contains the current versions of the files.
The git directory acts as a database for all the changes tracked in Git and the working tree acts as a sandbox where we can edit the current versions of the files.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
